https://www.tugraz.at/en/about-this-page/legal-notice/

TU Graz
Focus on TU GrazUniversityOverview: UniversityTU Graz at a GlanceOrganisational BasisMission StatementKey Objectives and Focus AreasTU Graz Portfolio of Affiliated CompaniesHistoryBuildings of TU GrazUniversity GazettesWorking at TU GrazOverview: Working at TU GrazJob VacanciesProfessorshipsStarting Work at TU GrazStaff PolicyServices for EmployeesOverview: Living in Graz for EmployeesServicesOverview: ServicesNews+StoriesFollow TU GrazTU Graz eventsMedia ServiceProjects with CompaniesForm a Partnership with TU GrazPublish Job VacanciesServices for Children and Young PeopleTU Graz LibraryArchive ResearchServices for AlumniChildcareOrganisational StructureOverview: Organisational StructureOrganisational ChartRectorate of TU GrazSenate of TU GrazUniversity Council of TU GrazDeansService Departments and Staff UnitsRepresentative Bodies for Members of TU GrazCommittees
Studying and Teaching
Focus on Studying and TeachingDegree and Certificate ProgrammesOverview: Degree and Certificate ProgrammesBachelor's Degree ProgrammesMaster's Degree ProgrammesTeacher Education ProgrammeDoctoral ProgrammesContinuing EducationStudying at TU GrazOverview: Studying at TU GrazProspective StudentsNew StudentsStudentsGraduatesInternational: Studying and TeachingOverview: International: Studying & TeachingStudy AbroadExchange at TU GrazDegree Seeking StudentsWelcome CenterTeaching AbroadInternational Teaching StaffInternational BlogInternational Cooperation VenturesNostrificationSummer Schools and Summer ProgrammesInternational Student AmbassadorsInternationals at TU Graz - COVID-19 InformationTeaching at TU GrazOverview: Teaching at TU GrazTeaching at TU Graz NewsStrategy of Academic AffairsDialogue Formats and EventsHigher Education DevelopmentHigher Education DidacticsEducational TechnologyServices for Teaching StaffPrize for Excellence in TeachingCooperation in TeachingStudent Mentoring
Research
Focus on ResearchFields of ExpertiseOverview: Fields of ExpertiseAdvanced Materials ScienceHuman & BiotechnologyInformation, Communication & ComputingMobility & ProductionSustainable SystemsResearch at TU GrazOverview: Research at TU GrazServices for ResearchersResearch Cooperation VenturesERC Grants at TU GrazChristian Doppler (CD) LaboratoriesDoctoral SchoolsTU Graz Research PortalResearch and BusinessOverview: Research and BusinessProjects with CompaniesForm a Partnership with TU GrazPublish Job VacanciesCompetence Centres and Research CompaniesBusiness Enterprises ñ Start-ups and Spin-offsInternational ResearchOverview: International ResearchResearch Stays AbroadResearch Stays at TU GrazResearch and Technology Advisory Committee
Faculties and Institutes
Overview: Faculties and InstitutesFaculty of ArchitectureFaculty of Civil EngineeringFaculty of Electrical and Information EngineeringFaculty of Computer Science and Biomedical EngineeringFaculty of Mechanical Engineering and Economic SciencesFaculty of Mathematics, Physics and GeodesyFaculty of Technical Chemistry, Chemical and Process Engineering, Biotechnology
Information for...
Quick LinksProspective StudentsResearchersTeaching StaffPupilsInternationalsCompaniesNew StudentsContinuing EducationMedia RepresentativesAlumniProspective Employees
DELegal Notice
Main Menu
TU GrazGraz University of TechnologySCIENCEPASSIONTECHNOLOGY
TU Graz/ About this page
Up to TU GrazWelcome to the TU Grazís New WebsiteFeedbackLegal NoticePrivacy PolicyDatenschutzerkl‰rung screenshots.tugraz.at
Legal Notice
Publisher
Graz University of Technology† Rechbauerstraﬂe 12 † 8010 Graz, Austria
Tel.: +43 316 873 0 † Fax: +43 316 873 6009 Email: infonoSpam@tugraz.at
Privacy
Privacy Statement (Datenschutzerkl‰rung) For more information on privacy, please see http://datenschutz.tugraz.at
Technical implementation and layout
Information Technology Services (ZID) of Graz University of Technology
Supervisory authority of Graz University of Technology
Federal Ministry of Education, Science and Research https://www.bmbwf.gv.at
Copyright
The information provided by the individual institutes and other facilities of Graz University of Technology as well as the other information providers is compiled independently by them, and entered into the system.
© Copyright ñ unless otherwise indicated ñ of the authors or of Graz University of Technology
VAT registration number
ATU 574 77†929
Liability
The entire content of the TU Graz website has been compiled with the greatest care and to the best of our knowledge. However, we can assume no liability for the actuality, completeness and correctness of all the web pages. Content shall be removed immediately from the time that knowledge of a specific infringement of rights is obtained; TU Graz shall not be held liable before this time.
The TU Graz website contains links to the websites of third parties; TU Graz has no influence over the content of such websites and shall therefore assume no liability for them.
The relevant information provider of the website shall be held responsible for the content and correctness of this information. When the link to the website of the third party was inserted, no infringements of rights were discernible. If TU Graz is made aware of an infringement of rights, the relevant link shall be removed immediately.
The content and works published on this website are subject to copyright. Any kind of reproduction, editing, dissemination and any kind of use beyond the limits of the copyright shall require the prior written consent of the relevant author.
When a user visits a website of TU Graz, information about his/her access (for example, the date, time, page accessed) can be stored. This does not constitute any analysis of personal data (e.g. name, address or email address). If personal data is collected, this is done so with the prior consent of the website user. Any transmission of the data to third parties shall not take place without the userís express consent.
TU Graz states explicitly that the transmission of data on the Internet (e.g. by email) can pose security risks. Complete data protection against access by third parties cannot be guaranteed. TU Graz shall assume no liability for any damage incurred as a consequence of such security risks. The use of published contact details by third parties for the purpose of advertising is explicitly prohibited. TU Graz reserves the right to take legal action in the event that unsolicited advertising information is sent (e.g. in the form of spam emails).
Open FooterClose Footer
Top
Graz University of TechnologyRechbauerstraﬂe 128010 GRAZAUSTRIAPhone: +43 316 873 0 Fax: +43 316 873 6009E-Mail: infonoSpam@tugraz.atwww.tugraz.atCampus mapOpening hours: 6 am ñ 8 pm
Information and service points
Campus Alte TechnikRechbauerstraﬂe 12Phone: +43 316 873 6560portier.alte-techniknoSpam@tugraz.at
Campus Neue TechnikStremayrgasse 16Phone: +43 316 873 6570portier.neue-techniknoSpam@tugraz.at
Campus InffeldgasseInffeldgasse 25DPhone: +43 316 873 6580portier.inffeldnoSpam@tugraz.at
Campus-Management-System TUGRAZonline
Intranet TU4U
E-Learning-Plattform TeachCenter
COVID-2019 (Ñcoronavirusì)
Information from TU Graz on dealing with COVID-2019
News+Stories Library Job Vacancies Media Service Events
Follow TU Graz
www.tugraz.at/go/follow
Legal Notice Privacy Policy Feedback
Accessibility
Tip: Use Ctrl + and Crtl - to change the font size.
Accept all cookies
Cookie-Categories:
Functional
Analysis
Marketing
We use cookies in order to be able to provide you with the best possible service in the future. In the privacy policy you will find further information as well as the possibility of withdrawal.Save preferences
